<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-06-09T05:54:28+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">JP4Kid - Child Protection Resources</title><subtitle>Save the Children defines child protection as measures and structures to prevent and respond to abuse, neglect, exploitation and violence affecting children.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Understand the Terms</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/learn/Understand-the-terms.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Understand the Terms" /><published>2025-06-09T02:38:09+08:00</published><updated>2025-06-09T02:38:09+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/learn/Understand-the-terms</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/learn/Understand-the-terms.html"><![CDATA[<p>#Convention on the Rights of the Child; CRC
Everyone is entitled to all the rights and freedoms set forth therein, without distinction of any kind, such as race, colour, sex, language, religion, political or other opinion, national or social origin, property, disability, birth or other status.
Childhood is entitled to special care and assistance.
A Child means every human being below the age of eighteen years (unless under the law applicable to the child, majority is attained earlier).
The best interests of the child shall be a primary consideration. Ensure the child such protection and care as is necessary for his or her well-being.</p>

<p>#Toxic Stress</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="learn" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[#Convention on the Rights of the Child; CRC Everyone is entitled to all the rights and freedoms set forth therein, without distinction of any kind, such as race, colour, sex, language, religion, political or other opinion, national or social origin, property, disability, birth or other status. Childhood is entitled to special care and assistance. A Child means every human being below the age of eighteen years (unless under the law applicable to the child, majority is attained earlier). The best interests of the child shall be a primary consideration. Ensure the child such protection and care as is necessary for his or her well-being.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Save Children starting from Violence Prevention</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/learn/save-children.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Save Children starting from Violence Prevention" /><published>2025-06-09T02:18:09+08:00</published><updated>2025-06-09T02:18:09+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/learn/save-children</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/learn/save-children.html"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="learn" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry></feed>